RG 062:131, Town of Southington
Connecticut State Library
- Series 9. Borough Records, 1890-1970; bulk 1900-1948
  - Financial records, 1890-1948 (Box 83)
    - Accounts receivable paid (Box 83)
      - Sewer repairs, 1943-1945 (Box 83, Folder 27)
      - Sewer repairs, 1946-1947, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 28)
      - Sewer assessments; sewer rentals; sidewalk assessments; sidewalk repairs, 1943-1947 (Box 83, Folder 29)
      - Highways; police; zoning; miscellaneous, 1943-1947 (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Audit reports (Box 83)
      - 1914-1931 (Box 83, Folder 31)
      - 1945-1947 (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - Bond issue of 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - Bond coupons, 1922-1929 (Box 93)
    - Bond issue of 1946, 1945-1946 (Box 83, Folder 34)
    - Budget, 1922-1923, 1945-1946 (Box 83, Folder 35)
    - Cancelled checks, 1922-1924 (Box 93)
    - Cancelled checks, 1924-1929 (Box 94)
    - Cash books
      - 1907-1921 (Volume Item 95)
      - 1921-1931 (Volume Item 96)
    - Journals
      - 1907-1934 (Volume Item 97)
      - 1944-1948 (Volume Item 98)
    - Ledgers
      - 1907-1936 (Volume Item 99)
      - 1927-1947 (Volume Item 100)
      - 1930-1936 (Volume Item 101)
    - Notes paid
      - 1931-1933, undated (Box 83, Folder 36)
      - 1941-1946 (Box 83, Folder 37)
    - Orders, 1890-1900 (Volume Item 102)
    - Payroll (Box 103)
      - Highway, 1939 November 18-1941 March 22; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Highway, 1941 March 29-1942 August 1; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Highway, 1942 August 8-1944 June 3; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Highway, 1947 March 1-1948 April 10; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Sewer, 1939 November 18-1941 March 22; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Sewer, 1941 March 29-1942 August 1; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Sewer, 1942 August 8-1944 June 3; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Sewer, 1947 March 1-1948 April 10; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Victory tax, 1944; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Victory tax, 1945; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Withholding tax, 1946; 1 volume (Box 103)
      - Withholding tax, 1947; 1 volume (Box 103)
    - Receipts and Expenditures
      - 1941-1944 (Volume Item 104)
      - 1935-1944 (Volume Item 105)
    - Treasurer's report, 1940, 1944 (Box 83, Folder 38)
  - Gasoline tank permits, 1914-1919 (Box 83, Folder 39)
  - Health officer, 1925-1944 (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - High School Site Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 83, Folder 41-43)
  - Holcomb School ditching and draining of swamp area, 1938-1939, undated (Box 83, Folder 44)
  - Insurance policies, 1927-1932, undated (Box 83, Folder 45-46)
  - Inventories, 1915-1931, undated (Box 83, Folder 47-48)
  - Licenses (Box 83)
    - 1914-1919 (Box 83, Folder 49)
    - 1942-1947 (Box 83, Folder 50)
  - Licenses, Liquor, 1945 (Box 83, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous, 1916, 1941, undated (Box 83, Folder 52)
  - Office supplies and equipment, 1938-1946 (Box 83, Folder 53)
  - Ordinances, 1922-1929, 1939-1945, undated (Box 83, Folder 54)
  - Permits, 1938, 1944-1946 (Box 83, Folder 55)
  - Personnel, 1940-1947 (Box 83, Folder 56)
  - Petitions (Box 83)
    - 1926-1931 (Box 83, Folder 57)
    - 1932-1933, 1938-1939 (Box 83, Folder 58)
    - 1940-1952, undated (Box 83, Folder 59)
  - Plumber bonds, 1931-1947, 1951-1953 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
  - Plumber licenses, 1931-1947, 1951-1953 (Box 84, Folder 5-7)
  - Police (Box 84)
    - Consolidation with town, undated (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1940, 1944-1947, undated (Box 84, Folder 9-10)
    - Financial, 1931-1944 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Job applications, 1929-1931, undated (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Monthly reports, 1942-1947 (Box 84, Folder 13-16)
    - Payroll, 1944-1946 (Box 84, Folder 17-19)
    - Personnel, 1926-1947, undated (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Rules and regulations, 1927, 1943, 1945 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Pool room permits, 1935-1940 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Pratt & Whitney, 1967-1970 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Public acts, 1915, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Real estate, 1914, 1926-1927, 1939-1947, undated (Box 84, Folder 25-26)
  - Real estate, Factory Square, 1942-1943 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Service charge notebooks, 1940-1945 (Box 84, Folder 28-29)
  - Sewers (Box 84)
    - Additions to sewer treatment plant (Box 84)
      - Application for federal assistance, approval of subcontractor, contract memorandcum, memorandum to applicant, project memorandum, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 30)
      - Contract, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 31-33)
      - Correspondence (Box 84)
        - Bailey, Howard, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 34)
        - Charter Oak Construction, 1943-1944 (Box 84, Folder 35)
        - Federal Works Agency, 1943-1944, undated (Box 84, Folder 36)
      - Insurance, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 37)
      - Payroll, 1943 October-December (Box 84, Folder 38)
      - Plans, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 39)
      - Sewer disposal plant improvement account, 1943-1944 (Box 84, Folder 40)
    - Agreements, 1915-1949 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Applications, circa 1910-1930
      - Academy Lane - Church Street (Box 88)
      - Cowle Avenue - Main Street to 199 (Box 89)
      - Main Street from 200 - Oakland Road (Box 90)
      - Old Turnpike - Woodruff Street, Miscellaneous (Box 91)
    - Assessment liens, 1915-1945 (Box 85, Folder 2-21)
      Arranged alphabetically.
    - Assessments, 1920-1956 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Carter Lane, Delahunty Drive and Hart Acre Road, Contract and specifications, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Connect orders, 1915-1916, 1929-1930 (Box 85, Folder 25-26)
    - Construction, 1913-1916 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Construction records, 1915-1925 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1914-1947, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 30-33)
    - Costs, Miscellaneous, 1925, 1941, undated (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - Hearing notices, 1923-1930, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 35)
    - Highwood Avenue (Box 85)
      - Assessmemts, 1929 (Box 85, Folder 36)
      - Contractor proposals, 1929 (Box 85, Folder 37)
    - Howard Avenue: Plan and profiles, 1949 (Box 85, Folder 38)
    - Index book, undated (Box 85, Folder 39)
    - Inspection reports, 1922, 1924, 1929-1941 (Box 85, Folder 40-41)
    - Journal, 1948-1951 (Box 85, Folder 42)
    - Knowles Avenue, Bids and contract, 1926 (Box 85, Folder 43)
    - Laboratory reports, 1922, 1927-1941 (Box 85, Folder 44-45)
    - Licenses, 1940-1943 (Box 85, Folder 46)
    - Miscellnaous, undated (Box 85, Folder 47)
    - Old Turnpike Road, Proposals, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 48)
    - Printed material, 914-1938 (Box 85, Folder 49)
    - Reports, 1929-1938 (Box 85, Folder 50)
    - Return receipts, 1913-1969 (Box 92)
    - Sewage settling tank, 1945 (Box 85, Folder 51)
    - Sewer index cards, 1915-1934 (Box 92)
      Arranged by street name then by street number.
    - Sewer street connection cards, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Sewerage plans, 1959, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Sidewalk insurance, 1941-1946 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Sidewalk liens, 1813m 1926, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Sign permits, 1933-1946 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Sinking fund, 1939, 1946 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Snow removal, 1937, 1942-1946, undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Special acts and ordinances, Supplement to, 1968 August 1 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Street lighting, 1919-1932, 1937-1946 (Box 86, Folder 88-89)
  - Streets (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, 1921-1947, undated (Box 86, Folder 10-11)
    - Maintenance, 1922, 1936-1942, undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous drawings, undated (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Receipts, 1937-1941, 1947 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Academy Lane, Description of layout, 1914 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Beecher Street, 1940, 1944 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Berlin Avenue (Box 86)
      - Description of layout, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1912, 1920, 1922 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Berlin Street, Sidewalks and curbs, 1916-1917 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Brooks, George, Germania Streets (Box 86)
      - Damages and benefits, 1916 (Box 86, Folder 20)
      - Hearing notices, 1916 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Brooks Street, Description of layout, 1916 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Center Street (Box 86)
      - Description of layout, 1913, 1918 (Box 86, Folder 23)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1912, 1919, 1922, 1941-1942 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Cheshire Turnpike (Box 86)
      - Bids and contract, 1943 (Box 86, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1938-1944, undated (Box 86, Folder 26)
      - Damages and benefits, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 27)
      - Hearing notices, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Eden Avenue (Box 86)
      - Damages and benefits, 1920-1921 (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1925 (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - George Street, Description of layout, 1916 (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Germania Street (Box 86)
      - Description of layout, 1916 (Box 86, Folder 32)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1925 (Box 86, Folder 33)
    - Grove Street, Description of layout, 1913 (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - Hart Acre Road, Map of Hart's Acres, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 35)
    - High Street, Sidewalks and curbs, 1913 (Box 86, Folder 36)
    - Highwood Avenue (Box 86)
      - Damages and benefits, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 37)
      - Description of layout, 1914, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 38)
      - Hearing notices, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 39)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1936-1938, 1946 (Box 86, Folder 40)
    - Hill Street, Description of layout, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 41)
    - Hillside Avenue, Description of layout, 1913 (Box 86, Folder 42)
    - Hobart Street, Street line, 1945-1946 (Box 86, Folder 43)
    - Knowles Avenue (Box 86)
      - Damages and benefits, 1925-1926 (Box 86, Folder 44)
      - Description of layout, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 45)
      - Hearing notices, 1925 (Box 86, Folder 46)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 47)
    - Liberty Street, Sidewalks and curbs, 1913 (Box 86, Folder 48)
    - Main Street (Box 86)
      - Damages and benefits, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 49)
      - Description of layout, 1908, 1913, 1936, 1934 (Box 86, Folder 50-54)
      - Hearing notices, 1913, 1921, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 55-57)
      - Monthly estimates, 1919-1920 (Box 86, Folder 58)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1920, 1922, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 59)
    - Maple Street (Box 86)
      - Damages and benefits, 1927-1928 (Box 86, Folder 60)
      - Description of layout, 1913, 1917 (Box 86, Folder 61-62)
      - Hearing notices, 1917, 1927 (Box 86, Folder 63-64)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1917 (Box 86, Folder 65)
    - Meriden Avenue, Sidewalks and curbs, 1917 (Box 86, Folder 66)
    - Merrell Avenue
      - Description of layout, 1913-1914 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Mill Street, 1946 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - North Liberty Street, Street line, 1946-1947 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Oak Street (Box 87)
      - Damages and benefits, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Decription of layout, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Hearing notices, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1922, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 8-9)
      - Specifications, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Old Turnpike, Hearing notices, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Safety Avenue (Box 87)
      - Description of layout, 1912 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Summer Street (Box 87)
      - Description of layout, 1913 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Hearing notices, 1913 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1917-1925 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Vermont Avenue, Sidewalks and curbs, 1914, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Vermont Court (Box 87)
      - Description of layout, 1921 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Hearing notices, 1921, 1922 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Water Street (Box 87)
      - Damages and benefits, 1921 (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Description of layout, 1921 (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - Hearing notices, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 22-23)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1921 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - West Center Street (Box 87)
      - Damages and benefits, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 25)
      - Description of layout, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 26)
      - Hearing notices, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 27)
      - Sidewalks and curbs, 1914-1915, 1925 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Tax records, 1900-1948 (Box 87)
    - Assessment lists
      - 1900-1907, 1 volume (Volume Item 106)
      - 1907-1913, 1 volume (Volume Item 107)
      - 1914-1927, 1 volume (Volume Item 108)
      - 1928-1937, 1 volume (Volume Item 109)
      - 1938-1944, 1 volume (Volume Item 110)
      - 1945-1948, 1 volume (Volume Item 111)
    - Collected, 1943-1944 (Box 87, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1946 (Box 87, Folder 30)
    - Property tax collected
      - 1941-1945, 1 volume (Volume Item 112)
      - 1945-1947, 1 volume (Volume Item 113)
    - Rate books
      - 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1928, 1930, 1931, 1931, 1932, 1933, 12 volumes (Box 115)
        There are two volumes for 1931, one of wihch does not include notations of taxes paid.
      - 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1941, 1942, 1945, 7 volumes (Box 116)
    - Refunds, 1931-1947 (Box 87, Folder 31)
    - Sewer assessment cash book, 1915-1923; 1 volume (Volume Item 114)
  - Tenement houses, 1941, undated (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Tree spraying, 1945 (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Traffic signals, 1928, 1938-1942 (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - Twilight league, 1934-1935 (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - War Production Board: Tracks on Eden Ave. and Bristol St., 1942-1943 (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Withholding tax, 1944-1945 (Box 87, Folder 37-38)
  - Zoning Board, 1938-1946, undated (Box 87, Folder 39)